Beautiful. Oh.
I don't think you want to have
the water in the picture,
right? You can take it off.
Yeah. Yeah, put it over there,
Nick. Come to this table as
well? Yeah, I might as well
take the table. Good. Very
good. Thank you. You know what
you can do, Nick? Sir. Put the
table back because it's missing
something. Put the table back
and put the water on the table
without the thing on top of it.
Okay. How's that look?
Go ahead take it in. Yeah.
Good. Right? Let's go.
Well it was a sad day but it
was a day where there was great
anger in our country. The
people went to Washington
primarily because they were
angry with an election that
they think was rigged. A very
small portion as you know went
down to the Capitol. And then a
very small portion of them went
in. But I will tell you they
were angry from the standpoint
of what happened in the
election. And because they're
smart and they see and they saw
what happened. And I believe
that that was a big part of
what happened on January sixth.
They thought because people
showed up to their rallies that
meant they were popular. The
idea that other people might be
sitting at home feeling
differently about it seems not
to have occurred to them. They
genuinely thought that must be
true. We won Georgia, we won
Michigan, we won Pennsylvania,
we won them all. As the
president has said, every
single vote needs to be counted
and needs to be heard and he
campaigned for the voiceless.
It's interesting to see Ivanka
Trump say that her father
wanted every vote to be counted
because Trump's mission in the
days after the election was to
stop the counting of votes. The
reality is people in this
country were getting multiple
ballots in the mail. There are
thousands and thousands of
people who are voting in
multiple states. There's no
evidence whatsoever that the
voter fraud that they're
claiming. But after weeks of
trying to overturn the results
of the election his legal team
has come up with nothing. So
far they've lost 30 cases. I
would love to release all the
information that I have. I
would love to give it to you
all. Except most of you
wouldn't cover it. All of the
legal documents and everything
else. It's not even a contest
but you still need a judge that
has courage and so far we
haven't found that judge.
Senate cabinet do not act. The
Congress may be prepared to
move forward with impeachment.
Seven forty-eight. That's when
I received it. But the house
members got it a while back.
Yeah, excellent.
Um but tell Zach to print me
off a hard copy for the trip
home. Sure. Great. I'm always
hopeful about America.